(this["webpackJsonpbca-mcq"]=this["webpackJsonpbca-mcq"]||[]).push([[0],{13:function(e,t,n){},14:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var s=n(0),o=n.n(s),a=n(2),r=n.n(a),i=n(3),c=n(4),l=n(7),u=n(5),m=(n(13),[{questionId:"1",question:"Program which is used to control system performance is classified as...",answers:["Experimental Program","System Program","Specialized Program","Organized Program"],correct:"System Program"},{questionId:"2",question:"Shell is the exclusive feature of...",answers:["UNIX","DOS","System Software","Application Software"],correct:"UNIX"},{questionId:"3",question:"A program is a...",answers:["device where information is stored","sequence of instructions","device that perform a sequence of operation specified by instruction in memory","none of these"],correct:"sequence of instructions"},{questionId:"4",question:"The software used to drive microprocessor based system is called...",answers:["firmware","assembly language of program","flowchart instruction","BASIC interpreter instruction"],correct:"assembly language of program"},{questionId:"5",question:"How many types of  main software are there ?",answers:["1","2","3","4"],correct:"2"},{questionId:"6",question:"What is the full form of SDLC ?",answers:["Software development live cycle","Software development leaf cycle","Software development life cycle","Software development life changing"],correct:"Software development life cycle"},{questionId:"7",question:"Which one of the following is not a part of SDLC ?",answers:["Designing","Testing","Hosting","Coding"],correct:"Hosting"},{questionId:"8",question:"Which of the following is a SDLC model ?",answers:["Decremental Model","Big Bang Model","Elite Model","X-Model"],correct:"Big Bang Model"},{questionId:"9",question:"Which of the following is not a type of Feasibility Study ?",answers:["Economical Feasibility","Operational Feasibility","Technical Feasibility","Client Feasibility"],correct:"Client Feasibility"},{questionId:"10",question:"What are the attributes of software products ?",answers:["Realibility","Robustness","None","Realibility and Robustness"],correct:"None"},{questionId:"11",question:"RAD model has",answers:["3 Phases","5 Phases","2 Phases","6 Phases"],correct:"5 Phases"},{questionId:"12",question:"During software development, which factor is most crucial ?",answers:["Product","Process","People","Project"],correct:"People"},{questionId:"13",question:"First level of prototype is evaluated by...",answers:["Tester","Developer","User","System Analyst"],correct:"Developer"},{questionId:"14",question:"Which of the following is an example of system software ?",answers:["MacOS","Chrome","VLC","Ms Office"],correct:"MacOS"},{questionId:"15",question:"Spiral Model was developed by...",answers:["Berry Boehm","Bev Little wood","Roger Pressman","Victor Basili"],correct:"Berry Boehm"}]),f=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:10;return Promise.resolve(m.sort((function(){return.5-Math.random()})).slice(0,e))},d=n(6),p=function(e){for(var t=e.question,n=e.options,a=e.selected,r=e.counter,i=n.length-1;i>0;i--){var c=Math.floor(Math.random()*i),l=n[i];n[i]=n[c],n[c]=l}var u=Object(s.useState)(n),m=Object(d.a)(u,2),f=m[0],p=m[1];return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"questionCard"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"question"},o.a.createElement("h2",null,r+1,". ",t)),f.map((function(e,t){return o.a.createElement("button",{key:t,className:"answerBtn",onClick:function(){p([e]),a(e)}},e)})))},h=function(e){var t=e.score,n=e.playAgain;return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-board"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"score"},"You scored ",t," / 10 correct answers!"),o.a.createElement("button",{className:"playBtn",onClick:n},"Play again!"))},g=function(){return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"warning"},o.a.createElement("h2",null,"*_*Becareful*_*"),o.a.createElement("ol",null,o.a.createElement("li",null,o.a.createElement("p",null,"Every time you refresh the page questions will be change.")),o.a.createElement("li",null,o.a.createElement("p",null,"Once you select the answer remaining are hidden and you can't change your answer.")),o.a.createElement("li",null,o.a.createElement("p",null,"After completing all the questions you will be redirected to result page."))))},y=function(e){Object(l.a)(n,e);var t=Object(u.a)(n);function n(){var e;Object(i.a)(this,n);for(var s=arguments.length,o=new Array(s),a=0;a<s;a++)o[a]=arguments[a];return(e=t.call.apply(t,[this].concat(o))).state={questionBank:[],score:0,responses:0},e.getQuestions=function(){f().then((function(t){e.setState({questionBank:t})}))},e.computeAnswer=function(t,n){t===n?e.setState({score:e.state.score+1,responses:e.state.responses+1}):e.setState({responses:e.state.responses<10?e.state.responses+1:5})},e.playAgain=function(){e.getQuestions(),e.setState({score:0,responses:0})},e}return Object(c.a)(n,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){this.getQuestions()}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"title"},o.a.createElement("h1",null,"BCA MCQ TEST"),o.a.createElement("p",null,"Design and Develop by ",o.a.createElement("a",{href:"https://kcsajan.com.np",title:"Click for more info"},"Sajan Kc"))),o.a.createElement(g,null),this.state.questionBank.length>0&&this.state.responses<10&&this.state.questionBank.map((function(t,n){var s=t.questionId,a=t.question,r=t.answers,i=t.correct;return o.a.createElement(p,{counter:n,question:a,options:r,key:s,selected:function(t){return e.computeAnswer(t,i)}})})),10===this.state.responses?o.a.createElement(h,{score:this.state.score,playAgain:this.playAgain}):null)}}]),n}(s.Component);r.a.render(o.a.createElement(o.a.StrictMode,null,o.a.createElement(y,null)),document.getElementById("root"))},8:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(14)}},[[8,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.cdc5ebe8.chunk.js.map